LEONARD:
Okay, we've got power to the laser.
(Sheldon:)I should've brought an umbrella.
-What for? It's not gonna rain.
-I know.
(Sheldon:)But with skin as fair as mine,
moon burn is a real possibility.
That's a buzzinga, right?
(Sheldon:)One of my best, don't you think?
[HOWARD FEIGNS LAUGH]
Howard, double-check
the equatorial mount on the laser.
-We need it locked on the Sea of Tranquility.
-You got it.
(Howard:)Raj, no.
(Howard:)Billions of dollars have gone
into inventing the Internet...
(Howard:)...and filling it with pictures of naked women
so we don't have to peep through windows.
(Raj:)It's not like that.
I'm watching someone's TV.
(Raj:)The Good Wife is on.
(Raj:)I tell you,
this is my new Grey's Anatomy.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, what is that? What is that?
(Leonard:)Relax, it's just a dirty sock.
How on earth can you say "dirty sock"
and "relax" in the same sentence?